adventurekk.com 2016-10-18

# Privacy Policy｜Adventure.,Inc.

## Privacy Policy

Adventure Co., Ltd. ("the company") promises that upon handling the client's personal information, the company will comply with laws and regulations regarding protection of personal information, and will handle the personal information appropriately as detailed in the policy below.

#### About management of personal information

The company will make an effort to prevent the leakage, loss, or destruction of personal information it holds by implementing appropriate safety measures in compliance with laws, guidelines, and internal regulations. Additionally, the company will educate its employees on topics including appropriate handling of personal information to further reinforce the security of the client's personal information.

#### Obtaining personal information, and purpose of use

The company will only obtain the client's personal information when necessary, through appropriate methods. When the company intends to obtain personal information and solicits the information from the client directly via letter or Internet, the company will clearly state the purpose of use of the personal information. The company will use the personal information obtained for the following purposes, bounded by necessity:

  * In order to confirm enlistment in our e-mail delivery service, and to send e-mails to the client
  * In order to provide or improve the products and services used by the client, and to develop new services
  * In order to send information related to products and services provided by the company
  * In order to confirm receipt of applications to job openings and to contact applicants

#### Sharing of personal information with third parties

Excluding the following circumstances, the company will not share personal information with third parties:

  * When prior consent from the client is obtained
  * When sharing with a contractor appropriately monitored by the company, in order to achieve the purpose of use
  * When necessary to protect the life, body, or property of a person, and gaining the consent of the client is difficult
  * When required legally by a national institution, local public body, or a contractor of a national institution or local public body
  * When deemed legal based on the Act on the Protection of Personal Information or other law(s)
  * When necessary to exercise the company's rights

#### About updates

The company may make changes to this privacy policy, based on changes in legislature or other circumstances. In this event, we ask that you refer to this page and understand the company's privacy policy.

*Request to the client*

In order to safely use the website managed by the company, we ask that you do not publicly upload the personal information of others or yourself to the website managed by the company.

December 2007
